[
    {
        "name": "Uppvidinge GK",
        "holes": [
            {
                "front": "57.13924235661579,15.15145451773492",
                "mid": "57.13915113477271,15.15145451773492",
                "back": "57.13906498060335,15.151435837746087"
            },
            {
                "front": "57.138330128047734,15.150683968198292",
                "mid": "57.13841121594028,15.150604578245755",
                "back": "57.13849737163145,15.150478488321133"
            },
            {
                "front": "57.14165960944751,15.150978321798672",
                "mid": "57.14173308874701,15.151053041754",
                "back": "57.14184204054318,15.15113243170654"
            },
            {
                "front": "57.14531663005354,15.153436551924019",
                "mid": "57.14533689821657,15.153506601882142",
                "back": "57.145372367475154,15.153567311845844"
            },
            {
                "front": "57.14543762791994,15.157065235997042",
                "mid": "57.14543002738079,15.157130615957959",
                "back": "57.145419893326164,15.157214675907703"
            },
            {
                "front": "57.14278971437397,15.153130743948003",
                "mid": "57.142764377424406,15.15303267400663",
                "back": "57.14274157415498,15.15294394405967"
            },
            {
                "front": "57.145180612927554,15.154798811197592",
                "mid": "57.14521101527969,15.154812821189216",
                "back": "57.14524901818476,15.154822161183631"
            },
            {
                "front": "57.144724574647874,15.153888161741998",
                "mid": "57.144684037639905,15.153874151750374",
                "back": "57.14464350058752,15.153836791772706"
            },
            {
                "front": "57.1436289438208,15.152710693184575",
                "mid": "57.14358333833339,15.152687343198538",
                "back": "57.1435377327898,15.152654653218082"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "name": "Glasriket - Lilla banan",
        "holes": [
            {
                "front": "56.9025448,14.8688475",
                "mid": "56.9025497,14.8689625",
                "back": "56.9025378,14.8690624"
            },
            {
                "front": "56.9024181,14.8705054",
                "mid": "56.9023472,14.8705819",
                "back": "56.9022831,14.8705919"
            },
            {
                "front": "56.9007985,14.8701497",
                "mid": "56.9007426,14.8701212",
                "back": "56.9006870,14.8700900"
            },
            {
                "front": "56.8991246,14.8702301",
                "mid": "56.8990523,14.8702167",
                "back": "56.8989835,14.8701936"
            },
            {
                "front": "56.8995082,14.8690403",
                "mid": "56.8995890,14.8690221",
                "back": "56.8996726,14.8690000"
            },
            {
                "front": "56.9020554,14.8691496",
                "mid": "56.9021250,14.8690962",
                "back": "56.9021960,14.8690553"
            }
        ]
    }
]